[{"answer": "Well, the first half an hour was obviously horrendous because I woke up and -- you know was woken up by my son, looked up at the big house, saw 200-foot flames coming out of it, and knew my daughter, nephews, nieces, my mother, and friends were in the house.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "How are you coming to terms with what happened?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Were you surprised how fast this happened?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "She did.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "She scooped up your mother I think and actually helped carry her out of the house, is that right?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Not a pretty sight.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "The knight in naked shining armor?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm not very technical, sadly, and I finished writing \"Losing My Virginity,\" the sort of second edition of it, and it was, you know, close to going to press.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "It's a good question.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Which camp do you think you're in?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well, look, I believe in evolution.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Do you believe more or less in god since the day after your conversation over dinner?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I found myself on one of my balloon trips, where, you know, I was 99 percent definitely going to die crossing the Pacific.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Do you ever -- do you ever pray?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, look --", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "And despite the fact that you survived that, Richard, with your .1 percent, you still don't believe?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, I think why it is has been well reported.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "And what is the best, simplest way to get out of this tank?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Look, he -- I think he would have done quite well not to have been elected when he was elected and waited four years because you know he was -- you know he had the worst stack of cards of any president for a long time.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Are you impressed by the way he's handled this or disappointed?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I think that business leaders need to play a much bigger part in tackling a whole range of issues than business leaders have done in the past.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Do you think that we need more centers like this set up by businessmen like you, encouraging that kind of entrepreneurial zeal, which many think is gone from places like America now?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "There is -- I think the number one priority is for, you know, government to get rid of waste of spending.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What about Warren Buffett's idea that all very rich people like he and yourself should pay whacking more tax?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, look, Rick Perry seems to be in the forefront at the moment.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Richard, of all the runners and writers for the Republican race right now, who do you think may end up being the nomination to take on President Obama?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Well, it's very exciting at the moment and exactly a month today we unveiled the space port in New Mexico which is stunningly beautiful and right out in the middle of the desert.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "When do you expect to take your first spaceflight?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Are you going to be the guy that makes me come closer to my children?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "We've nearly reached 500.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "How many have you actually sold?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "And I asked him what he thought about your program.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Did you write that?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I wanted to hear you say \"petite scene stealer.\"", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "A petite scene stealer?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Yeah, 90 pounds.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Are you really 4 foot, 11?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Actually, no one knows this story, but this kind of sums it up.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Do you just have a tendency to spew something out you instantly regret?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Your queen.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "My queen?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Not just a admiral, he was the head of the entire military.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "You went up to a British admiral and asked him to get you a drink?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "The chief of our armed forces?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "That is right.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "You asked him to get you a drink?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Of course, twice.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Did you meet the queen?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Well, the first night was wonderful because you address her and you only touch her if she touches you.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "\"People Will Say We're in Love\" from \"Oklahoma,\" oddly know, which is where I'm from.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "What was it?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "\"People Will Say We're in Love.\"", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "So you think you stumbled on a secret love song story?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "And there was a little glimmer in her eye.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Isn't that sweet?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "HENOWETH: He's light.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "You go out with her, do you?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I think for me, what -- they always talk about the \"ah ha\" moments\" with Oprah.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What does she mean to you?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I certainly try.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Do you do that?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Piers, help.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "How can this happen?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Trust me, there will be a big cue in here.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Anyone?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I think the whole idea of having to be with someone all the time scared me, and like what would I do if I needed to be alone, go to the bathroom -- I don't know, just life.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I think they were fabulous guys.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you wish you'd married either one of those men?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "In my mind.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Didn't you have a little fling with George Clooney?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "You did go out with Aaron Sorkin?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "You put on your intelligent voice.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "I sounded kind of smart, right?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Piers, you know, I'm a Christian, too.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, you know, first of all, I won't say whether I vote -- who I voted for and who I will vote for because I don't think -- I'm not -- I wouldn't want to talk about that publicly.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Do you feel disillusioned by him?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I can't think of a worse job.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Can you imagine that job?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Deal.", "docId": "110914pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Deal?", "qSentId": 598}]